{
    "id": "6205e9eed1f54aeb9009ae59c3da13ec",
    "title": "Simple Or Complex",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He sold the house that belonged to his father.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d738c3c5c2f546c39d03daf38ab87233"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have no money that I can lend you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "760489b584ae4a28bd846f3960386a30"
        },
        {
            "question": "The marks that were left by the whip are still visible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1957890cdaff4008a286fd5c029f6f7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He prospered by the money he inherited from his father.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a47f339f35d449c69e2cdefd4992c672"
        },
        {
            "question": "A man who is dead has no worries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7e2364d426cd45079323a59f06d8846e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He sold his father’s house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d1e8ce251d44230bb928b40dc2c6774"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have no money to lend you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eeff4b983d5f454880e6b85284389d82"
        },
        {
            "question": "The marks left by the whip are still visible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ec0167f50524cd6b669c1e980910a7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He prospered by his father’s money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "744be9c5516b46daba53ca8e2a2fd9c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "A dead man has no worries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e4053dc9a07a4389a957a3940e252945"
        }
    ]
}